Guide to the Time Inc. Fortune Editorial Records 1951-2013 MS 3009-RG 8
New-York Historical Society
- Series II.A. Staff Writer Charles Burck Files, 1951-1985; 7.25 Linear feet in 10 record cartons
  - Auto Industry: Engines, Technology, 1974-1979 (Offsite-box 2892, Folder 2)
  - Auto Industry: GM Reference, 1972-1979, undated (Offsite-box 2892, Folder 3-4)
  - Auto Industry: Interviews, 1983, undated (Offsite-box 2892, Folder 5-7)
  - Auto Industry: Interviews: Collier,________ [RESTRICTED], undated (Offsite-box 2215, Item 1)
    1 audiocassette: analog; 4 in. x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. Label on cassette: "Collier Side"
  - Auto Industry: Interviews: Estes, Elliot Marantette (E.M.) [RESTRICTED], 1981 (Offsite-box 2215, Item 2)
    1 audiocassette: analog; 4 in. x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. Label on A Side: "E.M. Estes / C.G. Burck Part I 60 Min. 1-9-81"
  - Auto Industry: Interviews: Estes, Elliot Marantette (E.M.) [RESTRICTED], 1981 (Offsite-box 2215, Item 3)
    1 audiocassette: analog; 4 in. x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. Label on Side A: "E.M. Estes/C.G. Burck Part II 60 Min. 1-9-81"
  - Auto Industry: Interviews: Estes, Elliot Marantette (E.M.) [RESTRICTED], 1981 (Offsite-box 2215, Item 4)
    1 audiocassette: analog; 4 in. x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. Label on Side A: "E.M. Estes / C.G. Burck Part III 2:25 Min 1-9-81"
  - Auto Industry: Interviews: Estes, Elliot Marantette (E.M.) [RESTRICTED], undated (Offsite-box 2215, Item 5)
    1 audiocassette: analog; 4 in. x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. Labels on A and B Side: "Estes".
  - Auto Industry: Interviews: Jennings, E.E. [RESTRICTED], 1976 (Offsite-box 2215, Item 6)
    1 audiocassette: analog; 4 in. x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. Label on A Side: "EE Jennings 4Mar76 draft executives over". Label on B Side: "Jennings 4 Mar 76 To OMO".
  - Auto Industry: Interviews: McDonald,_______ [RESTRICTED], 1981 (Offsite-box 2215, Item 7)
    1 audiocassette: analog; 4 in. x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. Label on A Side: " DLM McDonald 4/6/81 1 and 2".
  - Auto Industry: Interviews: Murphy,_______ [RESTRICTED], undated (Offsite-box 2215, Item 8)
    1 audiocassette: analog; 4 in. x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. Label on A Side: [illegible]. Label on B Side: "Murphy _|_ P FOD".
  - Auto Industry: Interviews: Notes: General, 1980-1981, undated (Offsite-box 2892, Folder 8-10)
  - Auto Industry: Interviews: Notes: Earlier, 1976-1979, undated (Offsite-box 2892, Folder 11)
  - Auto Industry: Interviews: Notes: GM, 1976-1977, undated (Offsite-box 2892, Folder 12-13)
  - Auto Industry: 1980 Market, 1980, undated (Offsite-box 2892, Folder 14-15)
  - Auto Industry: Notes and Memoranda, 1980-1981, undated (Offsite-box 2892, Folder 16)
  - Auto Industry: Renault, undated (Offsite-box 2892, Folder 17)
  - Auto Industry: Rotary Charge Engine, 1970-1979, undated (Offsite-box 2892, Folder 18)
  - Auto Industry: XCar, 1977-1980, undated (Offsite-box 2892, Folder 19-20)
  - Bicentennial Issue: Corporation and Its Changing Environment, 1968, 1974-1976, undated (Offsite-box 2892, Folder 21-22)
  - California Wine, 1971, undated (Offsite-box 2893, Folder 1-2)
  - Cannon, Charlie: Notes, 1980, undated (Offsite-box 2893, Folder 3-4)
  - CEO Survey: 1976 Draft/Background, 1959, 1975-1976, undated (Offsite-box 2893, Folder 5-6)
  - Changing Corporation, 1974-1975, undated (Offsite-box 2893, Folder 7)
  - Class of 1942: New Army Portfolio, 1966, undated (Offsite-box 2893, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1966-1974, undated (Offsite-box 2893, Folder 9-10)
  - Correspondence: Corrections and Suggestions, 1973-1975, undated (Offsite-box 2893, Folder 11)
  - Drinking Habits, 1973-1977, undated (Offsite-box 2893, Folder 12-15)
  - Employee Share Ownership Trust, 1973-1976, undated (Offsite-box 2893, Folder 16-17)
  - Employee Stock Ownership Plan, 1974-1976, undated (Offsite-box 2893, Folder 18-19)
  - Government and Business: Research, 1972-1974, undated (Offsite-box 2893, Folder 20)
  - Government and Business: Research, 1973-1975, undated (Offsite-box 2894, Folder 1-2)
  - Interviews: Adelman of Cacina [RESTRICTED], 1971 (Offsite-box 2215, Item 1)
    1 audiocassette: analog; 4 in. x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. Label on Side 1: "Adelman of Cacina 21 DEC 71 - NYC Also Side 2". Label on Side 2: "Adelman - Beaws side 1".
  - Interviews: Jacobs, Neil H. [RESTRICTED], 1975 (Offsite-box 2215, Item 2)
    1 audiocassette: analog; 4 in. x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. Label on Side 1: " Jacobs 7 Feb 75 (Neil H Jacobs, UCLA)". Label on Side 2: "Jacobs".
  - Interviews: Jilhs [RESTRICTED], undated (Offsite-box 2215, Item 3)
    1 audiocassette: analog; 4 in. x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. Label on cassette: [illegible]
  - Interviews: Kelso, Louis [RESTRICTED], 1975 (Offsite-box 2215, Item 4)
    1 audiocassette: analog; 4 in. x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. Label on Side 1: "Kelso #1 Dec 18 75". Label on Side 2: "Kelso L, Dec 18 75".
  - Interviews: Kelso, Louis [RESTRICTED], 1975 (Offsite-box 2215, Item 5)
    1 audiocassette: analog; 4 in. x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. Label on cassette: "#2 Kelso Dec 18 75".
  - Interviews: Kelso, Louis [RESTRICTED], undated (Offsite-box 2215, Item 6)
    1 audiocassette: analog; 4 in. x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. Label on Side A: "Kelso". Label on Side B: "Buffmaker (4) Count is - 77 Peter Sebalku"
  - Interviews: Williams, Dean [RESTRICTED], 1975 (Offsite-box 2215, Item 7)
    1 audiocassette: analog; 4 in. x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. Label on cassette: "Dean Harold Williams, UCLA GSM 6 Feb 75 Full Side".
  - Interviews: Williams, Dean [RESTRICTED], 1975 (Offsite-box 2215, Item 8)
    1 audiocassette: analog; 4 in. x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. Label on Side 1: "Dean Williams NYC 11 Feb 75". Label on Side 2: "Williams - about 3/4 of side".
  - John Deere, 1951-1953, 1964, 1973-1977, undated (Offsite-box 2894, Folder 3-4)
  - Lufkin, Dan, 1971, undated (Offsite-box 2894, Folder 5)
  - Memoranda and Letters, 1964-1977, undated (Offsite-box 2894, Folder 6-7)
  - Moonport, 1965-1966, undated (Offsite-box 2894, Folder 8)
  - Ohio Valley Portfolio, 1965-1966, undated (Offsite-box 2894, Folder 9)
  - Plate Wars: First Edits, 1982, undated (Offsite-box 2894, Folder 10-11)
  - Vietnam Logistics, 1966, undated (Offsite-box 2894, Folder 12)
  - Winship, H. Dillon, 1970, 1976-1978 (Offsite-box 2894, Folder 13)
  - Youth, 1968-1969, undated (Offsite-box 2894, Folder 14-15)
  - Youth Activism: General, 1967-1968, 1985, undated (Offsite-box 2894, Folder 16-19)
  - Youth Activism: Academic Papers, 1967-1968, undated (Offsite-box 2894, Folder 20)
  - Youth Activism: Booklets and Pamphlets, 1966-1968, undated (Offsite-box 2895, Folder 1-3)
  - Youth Activism: Brown, Charlie, undated (Offsite-box 2895, Folder 4)
  - Youth Activism: Bumper Sticker, undated (Offsite-box 2895, Folder 5)
  - Youth Activism: Clippings, Newsletters, and Magazines, 1964-1968, undated (Offsite-box 2895, Folder 6-7)
  - Youth Activism: Flyers, 1967, undated (Offsite-box 2895, Folder 8)
  - Youth Activism: Independent Newspapers, 1968-1976, undated (Offsite-box 2895, Folder 9-19)
  - Youth Activism: Independent Newspapers, 1967-1972, undated (Offsite-box 2896)
  - Youth Activism: Independent Newspapers, 1967-1971, undated (Offsite-box 2897)
  - Youth Activism: Independent Newspapers, 1968, undated (Offsite-box 2898, Folder 1)
  - Youth Activism: Photographs, undated (Offsite-box 2898, Folder 2)
  - Youth Activism: Research Guide, undated (Offsite-box 2898, Folder 3)
  - Youth Activism: Transcripts, undated (Offsite-box 2898, Folder 4)
- Series II.B. Staff Writer Rush Loving Jr. Interview Audiotapes [RESTRICTED], 1977; .25 Linear feet in 1 record carton
  Rush Loving Jr. was a staff writer for Fortune from 1969 to 1979. While working for the magazine, much of Loving's writing focused on the transportation industry.
  Citation:
  "A Conversation with The Times-Dispatch: Rush Loving Jr., a Man Who Loves Trains." Richmond Times-Dispatch. September 13, 2015. Accessed December 10, 2018. https://www.richmond.com/opinion/our-opinion/a-conversation-with-the-times-dispatch-rush-loving-jr-a/article_75e84f9e-4333-5327-a74e-8f9370316359.html.
  The Rush Loving Jr. Interview Audiotapes is entirely audiovisual material comprising four audiocassettes of interviews that Loving conducted with Averell Harriman, a former governor of New York State and United States diplomat. While the cassettes do not indicate why the interviews were conducted, Loving published an article shortly after the conclusion of the interviews on Harriman's memories of his father, railroad tycoon E. H. Harriman. The close proximity of the interviews with the publication of the article suggests the two are related. Fortune published the article "W. Averell Harriman Remembers Life with Father" in the May 8, 1978 issue.
  Unreformatted audiovisual material in the collection is not accessible.
  Oser, Alan S. "Ex-Gov. Averell Harriman, Adviser to 4 Presidents, Dies." The New York Times. July 27, 1986. Accessed December 10, 2018. https://www.nytimes.com/1986/07/27/obituaries/ex-gov-averell-harriman-adviser-to-4-presidents-dies.html.
  Twing, Stephen W. Myths, Models and U.S. Foreign Policy: The Cultural Shaping of Three Cold Warriors. Boulder, CO: Lynne Rienner Publishers, 1998.
  Arranged in original order.
  - Averell Harriman: 1st Interview: 1977 Dec. 12 [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box 2215, Item 1)
    1 audiocassette: analog; 4 in. x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. Label on case: "Interview with Averell Harriman Conducted by Rush Loving, Jr./FORTUNE 12 December 1977 Interview #1". Label on A Side: "(1) Averell Harriman 1st Interview - Dec. 12, 1977 Side #1 Rush Loving". Label on B side: "(2) Harrimab 1st Inter. 2nd part__(Side 2) Rush Loving Jr."
  - Averell Harriman: 2nd Interview: 1977 Dec. [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box 2215, Item 2)
    1 audiocassette: analog; 4 in. x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. Label on case: "Interview with Averell Harriman Conducted by Rush Loving, Jr./FORTUNE December 1977 Interview #2". Label on A Side: "(3) Harriman - 2nd Interview Side 1 (Side 3) Rush Loving". Label on B Side: "(4) Harriman - 2nd Interview 2nd Side (Side 4)".
  - Averell Harriman: 2nd and 3rd Interviews: 20 Dec. 1977 [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box 2215, Item 3)
    1 audiocassette: analog; 4 in. x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. Label on case: "Interview with Averell Harriman Conducted by Rush Loving, Jr./FORTUNE 20 December 1977 Interviews #2 and #3". Label on A Side: "(5) Averell Harriman Interviews 2 and 3 (Side 5) Rush Loving Jr." Label on B Side: "(6) Harriman 3rd Session - pt. 2 Side 6 _ Rush Loving Jr."
  - Averell Harriman: 3rd Interview: 20 Dec. 1977 [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box 2215, Item 4)
    1 audiocassette: analog; 4 in. x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. Label on case: "Interview with Averell Harriman Conducted by Rush Loving, Jr./FORTUNE 12 December 1977 Interview #3". Label on A Side: "(1) Harriman pt. 3-3 Interview Dec 20, 1977 (Side 7) Prop. of Rush Loving Jr.".
- Series III. Art Department Files, 1964-1982; 5 Linear feet in 6 record cartons
  The Art Department files contain materials produced while planning and creating issues of Fortune. All the materials were used to create issues of Fortune in 1982 but supplemental materials are included. The supplemental materials were used as references and may be from an earlier period than the magazine issue that was being produced. Included in this series are picture and caption layouts, magazine page mockups, correspondence about issues encountered while planning page layouts, handwritten notes, press kits, industry reports, press releases, photographs, slides, photo proofs, pamphlets, lists of reference, lists of assignments, article drafts, lists of event attendees, clippings, editorial schedules, and lists of acknowledgments.
  Organized as per the original order.
  - 1982 Oct. 4 Issue (Offsite-box 2887, Folder 12)
  - 1982 Oct. 4 Issue: Environmental Superlobby, 1982, undated (Offsite-box 2887, Folder 13)
  - 1982 Oct. 4 Issue: Fifth Generation, 1982, undated (Offsite-box 2887, Folder 14)
  - 1982 Oct. 4 Issue: In the News, 1982, undated (Offsite-box 2887, Folder 15)
  - 1982 Oct. 4 Issue: KORF, 1982, undated (Offsite-box 2887, Folder 16-17)
  - 1982 Oct. 4 Issue: MITI Interview, 1982, undated (Offsite-box 2887, Folder 18)
  - 1982 Oct. 4 Issue: Mortgage Banking, 1982, undated (Offsite-box 2887, Folder 19)
  - 1982 Oct. 4 Issue: Pensions, 1982, undated (Offsite-box 2887, Folder 20)
  - 1982 Oct. 4 Issue: Senator Dole, 1982, undated (Offsite-box 2887, Folder 21)
  - 1982 Oct. 4 Issue: Venture Capital, 1982, undated (Offsite-box 2887, Folder 22)
  - 1982 Oct. 18 Issue, 1982, undated (Offsite-box 2887, Folder 23)
  - 1982 Oct. 18 Issue: Boeing/Air Bus, 1982, undated (Offsite-box 2887, Folder 24)
  - 1982 Oct. 18 Issue: Business Lobby, 1982, undated (Offsite-box 2887, Folder 25)
  - 1982 Oct. 18 Issue: Convertibles, 1982, undated (Offsite-box 2887, Folder 26)
  - 1982 Oct. 18 Issue: E2 Prom, 1982, undated (Offsite-box 2888, Folder 1)
  - 1982 Oct. 18 Issue: E2 Prom [RESTRICTED], 1982, undated (Offsite-box R42)
  - 1982 Oct. 18 Issue: Ford in Europe, 1981-1982, undated (Offsite-box 2888, Folder 2)
  - 1982 Oct. 18 Issue: IAR Starter/Bandix, United, 1982, undated (Offsite-box 2888, Folder 3)
  - 1982 Oct. 18 Issue: In the News, 1982, undated (Offsite-box 2888, Folder 4)
  - 1982 Oct. 18 Issue: Portfolio: Farm, Babolna, Hungary, 1982, undated (Offsite-box 2888, Folder 5)
  - 1982 Oct. 18 Issue: Public Radio, 1982, undated (Offsite-box 2888, Folder 6)
  - 1982 Oct. 18 Issue: OYOT Wind Surfacing, 1982, undated (Offsite-box 2888, Folder 7)
  - 1982 Sept. 6 Issue, 1982, undated (Offsite-box 2888, Folder 8)
  - 1982 Sept. 6 Issue: Armstrong Tire, 1982, undated (Offsite-box 2888, Folder 9)
  - 1982 Sept. 6 Issue: Computers on Main Street, 1982, undated (Offsite-box 2888, Folder 10-11)
  - 1982 Sept. 6 Issue: DeBeers, 1975-1983, undated (Offsite-box 2888, Folder 12)
  - 1982 Sept. 6 Issue: First Boston, 1982, undated (Offsite-box 2888, Folder 13)
  - 1982 Sept. 6 Issue: Hotels Portfolio, 1980-1982, undated (Offsite-box 2888, Folder 14-15)
  - 1982 Sept. 6 Issue: Reagan Economic Team, undated (Offsite-box 2888, Folder 16)
  - 1982 Sept. 6 Issue: Reagan's Economic Team [RESTRICTED], undated (Offsite-box R42)
  - 1982 Sept. 6 Issue: Syms, 1982, undated (Offsite-box 2888, Folder 17)
  - 1982 Sept. 20 Issue, 1982, undated (Offsite-box 2888, Folder 18)
  - 1982 Sept. 20 Issue: Airplane - On the Road, 1982, undated (Offsite-box 2888, Folder 19)
  - 1982 Sept. 20 Issue: Beatrice Foods, 1982, undated (Offsite-box 2888, Folder 20)
  - 1982 Sept. 20 Issue: Books and Ideas: Global Insecurity, undated (Offsite-box 2888, Folder 21)
  - 1982 Sept. 20 Issue: Company Outings, 1981-1982, undated (Offsite-box 2888, Folder 22)
  - 1982 Sept. 20 Issue: ESCH, 1982, undated (Offsite-box 2888, Folder 23)
  - 1982 Sept. 20 Issue: Grumman, 1982, undated (Offsite-box 2888, Folder 24)
  - 1982 Sept. 20 Issue: Hydro Quebec, 1982, undated (Offsite-box 2888, Folder 25)
  - 1982 Sept. 20 Issue: TOSCA Chemical Lag, 1982, undated (Offsite-box 2888, Folder 26)
  - 1982 Aug 9 Issue: OYOT French Art, 1982, undated (Offsite-box 2888, Folder 27)
  - 1982 July 12 Issue, 1982, undated (Offsite-box 2889, Folder 1)
  - 1982 June 14 Issue, 1982, undated (Offsite-box 2889, Folder 2)
  - 1982 June 14 Issue: Anderson, Indiana, 1964, 1981-1982, undated (Offsite-box 2889, Folder 3)
  - 1982 June 14 Issue: Car Racing, 1975-1982, undated (Offsite-box 2889, Folder 4)
  - 1982 June 14 Issue: Economy, 1982, undated (Offsite-box 2889, Folder 5)
  - 1982 June 14 Issue: Oak Industries, 1982, undated (Offsite-box 2889, Folder 6)
  - 1982 June 14 Issue: Polls, 1982, undated (Offsite-box 2889, Folder 7)
  - 1982 June 14 Issue: Reichmanns, 1981-1982, undated (Offsite-box 2889, Folder 8)
  - 1982 June 14 Issue: Stewart McCarth/Oil, 1982, undated (Offsite-box 2889, Folder 9-10)
  - 1982 June 14 Issue: Unemployment, 1982, undated (Offsite-box 2889, Folder 11)
  - 1982 June 28 Issue, 1982, undated (Offsite-box 2889, Folder 12)
  - 1982 June 28 Issue: Cities Services, 1982, undated (Offsite-box 2889, Folder 13)
  - 1982 June 28 Issue: Cubs (Offsite-box 2889, Folder 14-15)
  - 1982 June 28 Issue: New Federalism, 1982, undated (Offsite-box 2889, Folder 16)
  - 1982 June 28 Issue: New Federalism [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R42)
  - 1982 May 3 Issue, 1982, undated (Offsite-box 2889, Offsite-box 17)
  - 1982 May 3 Issue: 500 Acts, 1982, undated (Offsite-box 2889, Folder 18)
  - 1982 May 3 Issue: AMA, 1982, undated (Offsite-box 2889, Folder 19)
  - 1982 May 3 Issue: Banking, 1982, undated (Offsite-box 2889, Folder 20)
  - 1982 May 3 Issue: DEC, 1982, undated (Offsite-box 2889, Folder 21)
  - 1982 May 3 Issue: DeLorean, 1982, undated (Offsite-box 2889, Folder 22)
  - 1982 May 3 Issue: Disinflation, 1982, undated (Offsite-box 2889, Folder 23)
  - 1982 May 3 Issue: Emery, 1982, undated (Offsite-box 2889, Folder 24-25)
  - 1982 May 3 Issue: Hidden Gems, 1980-1982, undated (Offsite-box 2889, Folder 26)
  - 1982 May 3 Issue: Intel, 1975-1982, undated (Offsite-box 2889, Folder 27)
  - 1982 May 3 Issue: Intel: Illustrations, 1982, undated (Offsite-box 2890, Folder 1)
  - 1982 May 3 Issue: Kaiser Steel, 1982, undated (Offsite-box 2890, Folder 2)
  - 1982 May 3 Issue: Merger of 1971, 1982, undated (Offsite-box 2890, Folder 3)
  - 1982 May 3 Issue: Office Automation, 1982, undated (Offsite-box 2890, Folder 4)
  - 1982 May 3 Issue: Oklahoma Play, 1982-1983, undated (Offsite-box 2890, Folder 5)
  - 1982 May 3 Issue: Top Industries: 500 Cover and Portfolio, 1981-1982, undated (Offsite-box 2890, Folder 6)
  - 1982 May 17 Issue, 1982, undated (Offsite-box 2890, Folder 7)
  - 1982 May 17 Issue: Artificial Intelligence, 1979-1982, undated (Offsite-box 2890, Folder 8-10)
  - 1982 May 17 Issue: Auto Styling, 1982, undated (Offsite-box 2890, Folder 11-12)
  - 1982 May 17 Issue: Freeze, 1982, undated (Offsite-box 2890, Folder 13)
  - 1982 May 17 Issue: Hospital Service, 1981, undated (Offsite-box 2890, Folder 14)
  - 1982 May 17 Issue: International Harvest, 1982, undated (Offsite-box 2890, Folder 15)
  - 1982 May 17 Issue: Japanese Roundtable, 1982, undated (Offsite-box 2890, Folder 16)
  - 1982 May 17 Issue: Material to Walter Bernaldi, 1982, undated (Offsite-box 2890, Folder 17)
  - 1982 May 17 Issue: McDermott, 1982, undated (Offsite-box 2890, Folder 18)
  - 1982 May 17 Issue: Nerve Gas, 1982, undated (Offsite-box 2890, Folder 19)
  - 1982 May 17 Issue: On Your Own Time: Outward Bound, 1981-1982, undated (Offsite-box 2890, Folder 20)
  - 1982 May 31 Issue, 1982, undated (Offsite-box 2890, Folder 21)
  - 1982 May 31 Issue: 7-Up, 1981-1982, undated (Offsite-box 2890, Folder 22)
  - 1982 May 31 Issue: Donovan, 1982, undated (Offsite-box 2890, Folder 23)
  - 1982 May 31 Issue: Donovan, 1982, undated (Offsite-box 2891, Folder 1)
  - 1982 May 31 Issue: Parts Like People Portfolio, 1981-1982, undated (Offsite-box 2891, Folder 2-3)
  - 1982 May 31 Issue: Private Industrial Lists, 1981-1982, undated (Offsite-box 2891, Folder 4)
  - 1982 May 31 Issue: Sotheby, 1982, undated (Offsite-box 2891, Folder 5)
  - 1982 May 31 Issue: Stroh, 1982, undated (Offsite-box 2891, Folder 6)
  - 1982 May 31 Issue: Unemployment/Small Town Portfolio, 1982, undated (Offsite-box 2891, Folder 7)
  - 1982 May 31 Issue: Real Estate, 1965, 1980-1982, undated (Offsite-box 2891, Folder 8-12)
- Series IV. Personnel and Contributors Files, 1951-1977; 2.5 Linear feet in 4 record cartons
  Personnel and Contributors files relate to Fortune staff, freelance writers, and sources who contributed to Fortune. The records do not include any official personnel records or reviews. Correspondence within the series notes that Fortune kept its own personnel files, but it is unclear if these records were held by a human resources department or the managing editor's office.
  Individual files contain information about what a specific person wrote or contributed to Fortune and appear to served for reference rather than as an official personnel file. While much of the material within the series appears to have been sent to managing editors, some items were sent to other staff who worked at Fortune. Materials in the series include reports on Fortune's forecasting capabilities, requests for payment, drafts of articles, raw reports, and correspondence. The correspondence discuss story ideas, research for articles, comments on articles, and internal issues within Fortune.
  - Albrook, Bob, 1967-1969, undated (Offsite-box 2898, Folder 5)
  - Alexander, Herbert, 1965-1969 (Offsite-box 2898, Folder 6)
  - Allner, Walter, undated (Offsite-box 2898, Folder 7)
  - Beardwood, Roger, 1966-1967, undated (Offsite-box 2898, Folder 8)
  - Bell, Daniel, 1954-1958, 1967, undated (Offsite-box 2898, Folder 9-10)
  - Bellak, Dr. Leopold, 1967-1968, undated (Offsite-box 2898, Folder 11)
  - Bello, Frank, 1960-1961, undated (Offsite-box 2898, Folder 12-13)
  - Boericke, William, 1965, undated (Offsite-box 2898, Folder 14)
  - Boorstin, Daniel J., 1966-1967, undated (Offsite-box 2898, Folder 15)
  - Bork, Robert H., 1961-1971, undated (Offsite-box 2898, Folder 16-17)
  - Bowen, William, 1966 (Offsite-box 2898, Folder 18)
  - Bradshaw, Thornton, 1976-1977 (Offsite-box 2898, Folder 19)
  - Bridges, Harry, 1967, undated (Offsite-box 2898, Folder 20)
  - Brittan, Samuel, 1969, undated (Offsite-box 2898, Folder 21)
  - Brown, William, 1976, undated (Offsite-box 2898, Folder 22)
  - Burck, Gilbert, 1953-1965, undated (Offsite-box 2898, Folder 23)
  - Bush, Vannevar, 1964-1965, undated (Offsite-box 2898, Folder 24)
  - Bylinsky, Gene, 1967 (Offsite-box 2898, Folder 25)
  - Cameron, Juan [empty], undated (Offsite-box 2898, Folder 26)
  - Chamberlain, John, 1960-1968, undated (Offsite-box 2898, Folder 27)
  - Chamberlain, John [RESTRICTED], 1960-1962 (Offsite-box R42)
  - Cone, Fairfax, 1965, undated (Offsite-box 2898, Folder 28)
  - Cordtz, Dan, 1962-1966, undated (Offsite-box 2898, Folder 29)
  - Cranston, Alan, 1964, 1970, undated (Offsite-box 2898, Folder 30)
  - Davenport, John, 1965-1967, undated (Offsite-box 2898, Folder 31)
  - Diebold, John, 1974, undated (Offsite-box 2898, Folder 32)
  - Drucker, Peter, 1962-1968, 1974 (Offsite-box 2898, Folder 33)
  - Ewing, John S., 1972-1973 (Offsite-box 2898, Folder 34)
  - Faltermayer, Edmund K., 1965-1967 (Offsite-box 2898, Folder 35)
  - Faltermayer, Edmund K. [RESTRICTED], 1960 (Offsite-box R42)
  - Freeman, Gaylord, 1971 (Offsite-box 2898, Folder 36)
  - Friend, Irwin, 1953-1956 (Offsite-box 2899, Folder 1)
  - Gart, Murray, 1966-1968, undated (Offsite-box 2899, Folder 2)
  - Glazer, Nathan, 1968-1970, undated (Offsite-box 2899, Folder 3)
  - Greenspan, Alan, 1968 (Offsite-box 2899, Folder 4)
  - Griffith and Banks: Memorandum on New Series and Reply [empty], undated (Offsite-box 2899, Folder 5)
  - Guzzardi, Walter, 1959, 1966-1967, undated (Offsite-box 2899, Folder 6)
  - Harris, William B., 1959-1960 (Offsite-box 2899, Folder 7)
  - Harris, William B. [RESTRICTED], 1960 (Offsite-box R42)
  - Herrera, Phil, 1967-1968 (Offsite-box 2899, Folder 8)
  - Johnston, Mary, 1965 (Offsite-box 2899, Folder 9)
  - Kahn, Herman, 1958-1959, 1965-1969, undated (Offsite-box 2899, Folder 10)
  - Kay, Hubert, 1962-1965 (Offsite-box 2899, Folder 11)
  - Keylor, Art, 1967 (Offsite-box 2899, Folder 12)
  - Klaw, Spencer, 1960-1970, undated (Offsite-box 2899, Folder 13)
  - Lapp, Dr, Ralph E., 1965-1968, undated (Offsite-box 2899, Folder 14)
  - Lenahan, Pat and Marie Cherichetti, 1966-1967 (Offsite-box 2899, Folder 15)
  - Lessing, Larry, 1966 (Offsite-box 2899, Folder 16)
  - Lichtenstein, Eugene, 1963, undated (Offsite-box 2899, Folder 17)
  - Lincoln, Freeman, 1962, undated (Offsite-box 2899, Folder 18)
  - Lionni, Leo, 1962-1964 (Offsite-box 2899, Folder 19)
  - Lubar, Robert, 1957-1967, undated (Offsite-box 2899, Folder 20)